[Music]
women in rural India spend their lives
taking care of their homes and their
families
but they neglect their own health
[Music]
this year's whom ICICI Lombard found a
unique way to help women take Health
into their own hands
millions of women attend the festival
and spend their days singing prayers
where clapping is intrinsic to this
ritual
[Music]
figured that the best way to get these
women to make time for their health was
to ask them to keep clapping
so we manufactured a special batch of
clapping gloves lined with studs that
triggered acupressure points every time
the wearer of the gloves clapped
these were given to women participating
in prayer sessions at home and every
time they clapped the gloves triggered
acupressure points helping clear sinuses
improve blood circulation Aid digestion
and other health benefits
[Music]
foreign
has introduced the Clapping gloves to
rural women in Gujarat and Rajasthan
what started off at will help
ensure that the health of India's rural
women remains in good hands
[Music]
thank you